If you are also porting your current health insurance, then
definitely watch this video and
save it. Before doing portability, my
dear, please clarify your purpose whether
I am doing portability for correction
or for some short term
benefit. If it is for short term benefit, then it is
not recommended. For
example, if someone is offering me a discount, then
I am porting, it is not a
good idea. For example, if a relative
or friend has taken an agency or I have got the
policy changed under his influence,
it is not a good idea. If I am doing it
for correction, for example, in
my current policy, there is
no service provider, that means there is
no intermediate, and that policy
is running through a bank or I have
purchased that policy from an online platform, even then
portability is a good idea. Currently, there are
too many sub-limits in my policy. There is
also an issue of pricing and
I want to go to the right pricing with the right limits. So,
portability is again a
Thirdly, if I am
facing any problem with my current advisor or intermediate, whether it
is problematic or there is no communication, then
also portability may be a good idea, so
always make the purpose clear before porting.